{
    "subject": "Todd_Manning",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Blair_Cramer",
    "human_readable": "Todd Manning is married to Blair Cramer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879922866821289,
            "question": "Is Blair Cramer married to Todd Manning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9056172966957092,
            "question": "Who is Todd Manning married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8841109871864319,
            "question": "To whom is Todd Manning currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7806527018547058,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Todd Manning and Blair Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726208925247192,
            "question": "What is the name of Todd Manning's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5608160495758057,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Blair Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17160962522029877,
            "question": "Is there a marriage mentioned in this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14383120834827423,
            "question": "Name one character married to another character in this statement."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10306718945503235,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.043773964047431946,
            "question": "Can you identify a couple mentioned in the statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Todd Manning is married to Blair Cramer.",
            "html": "yago_29635_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_29635_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one character married to another character in this statement.",
            "html": "yago_29635_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a marriage mentioned in this statement?",
            "html": "yago_29635_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29635_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Todd Manning is married to Blair Cramer\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support the statement \"Todd Manning is married to Blair Cramer.\" For example, multiple entries mention their relationship as a supercouple from the soap opera One Life to Live and details about their interactions and marriage status."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}